sokothemes.com 2013-10-29

# Privacy Policy

SokoThemes.com has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following statement discloses all of our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**1\. User / Customer Definitions  **

"Customer" or "Member" means any person gaining additional or paid access to products & services provided by SokoThemes.com

**2\. Children's Privacy  **

SokoThemes.com is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. SokoThemes.com does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13; nor do we target our web sites, products and/or services to children under the age of 13. 

**3\. Third Parties**

We have never shared our Customers' names with third parties; unless, a user has specifically requested to receive special offers or promotions with an advertiser found on our web site; or, if a user creates a public profile specifically for the purpose of being shared within an online community hosted or owned by SokoThemes.com. Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the Customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the Customer. We value your business and we respect your privacy. 

**4\. No Spyware / No Adware**

None of the software available from SokoThemes.com contains any form of spyware or adware. Software from third parties that SokoThemes.com may sometimes provide links for, is not within the control of SokoThemes.com. Therefore, third party software, may or may not contain forms of adware or spyware. We ask that you carefully read all license agreements related to any software product that you intend to download. 

**5\. Data Collected**

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. In addition, we use cookies and 1x1 pixels. Cookies and 1x1 pixels are used to deliver better services, provide account management, and targeted marketing messages to you, the web surfer. 

**6\. Registration Forms**

Our site registration forms require our customers to enter their email address, contact info, and sometimes personally identifiable information such as: email address, first name, last name, address, city, state, phone, date of birth, and postal/zip code. We use data provided through registration forms to send the user information about our company, create online community profiles, and to provide (or sell) various subscription services and/or other products. 

**7\. Network Security**

SokoThemes.com has put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information that is collected. Various security technologies have been implemented to ensure that external parties cannot access or modify Users' personal information on the SokoThemes.com website. Specifically, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption is used on specific Web pages to safeguard online purchase transactions. SSL technology is the industry standard protocol for secure, Web-based communications. 

**8\. Financial Information  **

Customer payment information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) are all processed securely through the PayPal. SokoThemes.com does not store any Customer financial information on it's own servers, OR in it's own databases; regardless of whether you enter your financial information at SokoThemes.com or directly through PayPal. For more information about PayPal and their privacy policies, please visit: ( www.paypal.com ).

**9\. Liability**

Our site contain links and advertisements for various other sites. SokoThemes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**10\. Cookies**

SokoThemes.com uses cookies to track whether or not visitors have seen or used our sites, products, and services. Cookies are also used for advertising and tracking of advertising campaigns. In some cases, cookies may be used to store account identification information, or customized user settings and preferences for SokoThemes.com. Some cookies may contain personally identifiable information. 

**11\. Abuse**

If someone abuses our system, we may disclose their IP address and any pertinent information we have about them to law enforcement agencies or other organizations involved in apprehending that person. In addition, SokoThemes.com reserves to the right to work directly with law enforcement agencies that subpoena SokoThemes.com for information related to any criminal investigation. 

**12\. Opt-Out**

You may opt-out of all the services, tools, products, and/or software that SokoThemes.com provides at any time you wish. To opt-out of COOKIES, please disable COOKIES on your browser. To opt-out or delete all of your accounts, email, profiles, and/or other memberships or subscriptions associated with SokoThemes.com; please contact us via email; with a request for termination of such services. 

**13\. Other Divisions Of SokoThemes.com**

Other sites and services powered by SokoThemes.com ( are separate divisions of SokoThemes.com ) and have their own privacy policy as well as terms & conditions of use; specifically related to the products and/or services they provide. Please read the legal section within any site powered by SokoThemes.com for further details. 

**14\. Contacting SokoThemes.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our company, or your dealings with our company, you can contact support using [our contact form](http://www.sokothemes.com/index.php?route=information/contact).
